Leszek¹ Pietrzak

• Birthday: January 21st, 1987

• **Current location**: CET Timezone

• Nationality: Polish

• **Phone**: <u>skype:smutnyleszek</u>

E-mail: leszek@magicznyleszek.xyz

Website: github.com/magicznyleszek

• Favourite color: black

¹if in doubt, try "lesheck"

I am a creator, I always loved building something new: be it through writing, drawing or coding. As for frontend development, I love that my work can be experienced live in the browser and that I can publish anything in just a few minutes.

The three values closest to my heart are: order, meaning and simplicity. I fear for the future of humanity, so I don't want to throw more senseless evil out there - I would love to take part in a meaningful, nature- and future-friendly projects. I try to maintain good work/life balance, so I avoid toxic environments.

Skills

I have strong frontend development skills with some backend experience. I can do identity design, UI design and illustration - I mainly use Illustrator, Sketch, Photoshop and InDesign. I am no stranger to Scrum, Kanban, recruitment, introducing new people into projects and copywriting. I'm familiar with all the OSs, but my favourite setup is MacOS with Atom.

Technologies I would love to work with: **TypeScript** or **ES6**, **Vue**, **React**, **Angular**, **NPM**, **cssnext** and **RESTful APIs**. I would also like to have **TDD**, **code reviews**, **pair programming**, **code linting** and good planning with estimations.

Some technologies I worked with: HTML (Twig), CSS (Compass, Sass, cssnext, BEM, MADCSS), JavaScript (TypeScript, CoffeeScript, ES6 [Babel], Angular, React, Vue, Alt, Backbone, Phaser, Lodash, jQuery, TweenMax), TDD (Karma, Jasmine, PhantomJS, Cypress, Selenium), Grunt, NPM, Git, CEF, Jekyll, MySQL, PHP (Symfony2), Jira, Asana.

Employment

March 2018 - now

Frontend Developer @ KoBoToolbox - remote - kobotoolbox.org

As part of a small team building new functionalities for a powerful open source data collection tools.

Some technologies here: ES6 [Babel], React, Reflux, Cypress, Sass, Webpack.

March 2007 - now

Illustrator, Designer & Web Developer @ freelancing - remote - magicznyleszek.xyz

I'm always open for small design and web jobs to give me opportunity to do something crazy and try something new. I also work on some open-source projects and tools on my spare time. Some cool web projects are:

- <u>Magicxer</u> combines words from list into a list of clever mixes (Parcel, Vue.js, Jest, TypeScript, Prettier)
- <u>Hues</u> color converter tool (React, Alt, ES6, RequireJS, Karma, cssnext, MADCSS)
- Mad Skeleton CSS boilerplate (Jekyll, Node, cssnext, MADCSS)
- <u>Humansjs</u> zero-player human existence simulator (Parcel, Jest, TypeScript)

November 2014 - May 2018

Frontend Engineer @ GOG.com - Warsaw, Poland - gog.com/galaxy

My main responsibility was creating a frontend of GOG Galaxy desktop application. I also develop some webapps and take part in recruiting new developers and introducing them to the project. During work here I took part in launching GOG Galaxy and creating The Witcher 3 game.

Technologies: TypeScript, ES6, Angular, Lodash, TDD (Karma, Jasmine, PhantomJS), Twig, Sass, BEM, MADCSS, CoffeeScript, Webpack, Grunt, NPM, Git, CEF, Jira, Asana

June 2013 - November 2014

Web Designer & Frontend Developer @ Clos Brothers - Warsaw, Poland - <u>closbrothers.pl</u>

I was working in a small team delivering websites and webapps for big clients (Toyota) and smaller, educational ones, too (Museum of the History of Polish Jews, Silesian Risings Museum).

Technologies: Angular, Phaser, jQuery, TweenMax, Compass, Jekyll, Twig, Symfony2, PHP, Grunt, Git, SVN.

October 2012 - July 2013

Graphic Designer & Web Developer @ Trewebs - Warsaw, Poland - trewebs.com

In this semi-startup, I was hired to design the UI and identity for diet app. As time went on, there were less design tasks and a need for developer arisen - as I was already familiar with HTML and CSS, I started to learn and work on some small web development projects.

Technologies: jQuery, Compass, Drupal, WordPress, PHP, MySQL

Education

September 2010 - September 2013

Graphic Design @ Wyższa Szkoła Nauk Humanistycznych i Dziennikarstwa - Poznań, Poland

Licentiate degree (~BA) with highest score (5)

September 2007 - September 2010

Cultural Studies @ Wyższa Szkoła Nauk Humanistycznych i Dziennikarstwa - Poznań, Poland

September 2006 - September 2007

Computer Science @ Adam Mickiewicz University - Poznań, Poland

Language skills

- Polish native
- English professional
- German basics
- **Spanish** basics
- Toki Pona basics

Interests

Antispeciesism with additional interest in feminism, the meaninglessness of life, unlistenable music, doodling and drawing, evolution of life, dinosaurs and the future of humankind, taboos and things NSFW.